Difficulty Level: King of Diamonds
Game: Impostor
All teams will be assigned one of two roles:
HUMAN... or IMPOSTOR
There can be more than one Impostor
per round
A computer science word will be revealed
to all human teams
The word will NOT be revealed
to the IMPOSTOR team
The HUMAN teams must correctly identify
the impostor.
The IMPOSTOR must conceal their identity
and deceive all others.
Teams will proceed individually
in an assigned order
Each team must submit a phrase,
no longer than THREE words.
The phrase must be related to the given word.
It is strictly prohibited to directly input the given word.
Your phrase will be judged, analyzed,
and questioned by other teams
Additionally, all teams, both human and impostor teams,
have the liberty to interact with the lotus flower during their turn
for a hint on the assigned word.
However, interacting with the flower alerts all teams in the game
during your turn, and drains the life of the lotus flower
as well as the surrounding environment.
The lotus flower can only be used ONCE
during your team's turn, meaning teams know you've used
the hint to your advantage and can become suspicious.
After all responses have been submitted,
all teams must vote for a suspected Impostor
Alternatively, teams can vote for an additional round,
with the same roles and term
The votes are tallied by the game system,
and the identities of each player are then revealed
to all screens
If the IMPOSTOR team is correctly identified,
all HUMAN teams are rewarded 2 points
for the duration of the game.
However, if the IMPOSTOR team survives,
the IMPOSTOR team is rewarded 5 points
for the duration of the game.
The point distribution marks the end of one round,
starting a new round with different roles
and different words
The game will last for 3 rounds.
By the end of the 3 rounds, the three team(s)
with the highest amount of points
receives a GAME CLEAR
All other teams will receive a GAME OVER
The IMPOSTOR game tests the extent
of your Computer Science knowledge,
as well as your ability to read or hide from others
The game will now begin.